export const prequiz = [
  {
    question: "A neural network is a network or circuit of neurons.",
    answer: 0,
    options: ["True", "False"],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "What 2 subjects are neural networks usually associated with?",
    answer: 1,
    options: [
      "Geology & Chemistry",
      "Biology & Artificial Engineering",
      "Geology & Biology",
      "Chemistry & Artificial Engineering",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "The fundamental unit of a network is?",
    answer: 2,
    options: ["The Brain", "A Nucleus", "A Neuron", "An Axion"],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "Neural Networks are complex _____ with many parameters",
    answer: 0,
    options: [
      "Linear Functions",
      "Discrete Functions",
      "Exponential Functions",
      "Nonlinear Functions",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is an application of Neural Networks?",
    answer: 3,
    options: [
      "Sales Forecasting",
      "Risk Management",
      "Data Validation",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
];

export const postquiz = [
  {
    question:
      "Normalization is the process of transforming or changing the columns in a dataset to a common scale.",
    answer: 0,
    options: ["True", "false"],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which is an example of a type of analysis Neural Networks can perform?",
    answer: 4,
    options: [
      "Binary Classification",
      "Regression",
      "Multivariate Classification",
      "Prediction",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "The number of training examples used in a single iteration is?",
    answer: 2,
    options: [
      "Epochs",
      "Loss Function",
      "Batch Size",
      "Optimazation Algorithm",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question: "The term Epoch refers to",
    answer: 1,
    options: [
      "A rate that controls the amount of change to the model in response to the estimated error each time the model weights are updated",
      "The number of passes a machine learning algorithm has finished in an entire training dataset",
      "The method by which a specific algorithm is observed to measure how well it models the given data.",
      "The percentage of data being used to train and teach the model the hidden features or patterns in the data.",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A process that compares numerous solutions iteratively until an ideal solution is identified.",
    answer: 3,
    options: [
      "Normalization",
      "Loss Function",
      "Learning Rate",
      "Optimization Algorithm",
    ],
    selected: null,
  },
];
